Jonah Sherman Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 4. Newspapers, 1840 - 1999; 4; Boxes: 55 - 74
  - Subseries 4.2: Loose Newspapers, 1886 - 1999; 4.2; Boxes: 62 - 70
    - Subseries 4.2.1: Poughkeepsie Journal (under other names), 1889 - 1999; 4.2.1; Boxes: 62 - 65
      - Subseries 4.2.1.4: Poughkeepsie Journal, 1963 - 1999; Box: 65
        - Poughkeepsie Journal - Bicentennial Edition, 1976 July 4 (Folder 6, Box 65)
        - Poughkeepsie Journal - "Independence", 1976 July 4 (Folder 7, Box 65)
        - Poughkeepsie Journal - "Then and Now", 1982 October 31 (Folder 8, Box 65)
        - Poughkeepsie Journal - "Century 1: Historic Moments 1785-1885, 1985 August 11 (Folder 9, Box 65)
        - Poughkeepsie Journal - "The Pride of Poughkeepsie, Riverfest: The Biggest Party in 300 years", 1987 June 2 (Folder 10, Box 65)
        - Poughkeepsie Journal - "Agency Head Has the Verve and the Vision", 1999 February 29 (Folder 11, Box 65)
        - Poughkeepsie Journal - "When Main Street was Hopping", 1999 March 14 (Folder 12, Box 65)
    - Subseries 4.2.2: The Sunday Courier, 1886 - 1930; 4.2.2; Box: 66
      - The Sunday Courier - volume XIV, number 18, 1886 May 2 (Folder 1, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - volume XV, number 15, 1887 April 10 (Folder 2, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - volume XVIII, number 34, 1890 August 24 (Folder 3, Box 66)
      - The Weekly Courier - volume IX, number 2, 1891 January 12 (Folder 4, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - "The Titanic Sunk at Sea; 1,635 Lives are Lost", 1912 April 21 (Folder 5, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - "Webb Predicts Million For Hospital Fund", 1924 November 14 (Folder 6, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - Vassar Hospital, 1924 November 14 (Folder 7, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - "Alderman Set to Down Fire Station Plan", 1929 March 10 (Folder 8, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - Second Section, 1929 March 10 (Folder 9, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - Other Page, 1929 March 10 (Folder 10, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - "Vassar College to Take Over Putnam Hall", 1929 March 17 (Folder 11, Box 66)
      - The Sunday Courier - "Program Completed For Bridge Dedication Tomorrow", 1930 August 24 (Folder 12, Box 66)
    - Subseries 4.2.3: The Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise, 1904 - 1939; 4.2.3; Box: 67 - 68
      - The Evening Star - "Czar"s Squadron is Near Tokyo", 1904 July 26 (Folder 1, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star -"Pres. Taft "Tells It" to Gov. Stubbs", 1909 May 15 (Folder 2, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "Nine-cent Trolley Fare in Ordered Here", 1924 November 15 (Folder 3, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "separate page", 1924 November 15 (Folder 4, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "June Heat Record Here Broken Today", 1925 June 4 (Folder 5, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "Webb asks $25,000 to Inquire into Vehicular Bridge at Hudson; Federal Officers Rain Six Places Here", 1926 January 26 (Folder 6, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "Thousands Gather for Bridge Opening; Roosevelt Planning a River Authority", 1930 August 25 (Folder 7, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - Bridge Opening Edition, 1930 August 25 (Folder 8, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "5 Youths Plead Guilty to Burglaries", 1931 May 8 (Folder 9, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "City Seeks WPA Playground Fund; Britain Demands League Stop Italo-Ethiopian War", 1935 September 11 (Folder 10, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "$460,360 WPA Program Approved; League Grants Ethiopia Arms and Cuts Off Italy", 1935 October 11 (Folder 11, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "Doctors Win Fight For Payment; Great Britain Protests Italian Attacks", 1935 October 31 (Folder 12, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - separate page, 1935 October 31 (Folder 13, Box 67)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "250th Birthday Nears Climax", 1937 October 12 (Folder 1, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "250th Birthday Nears Climax", 1937 October 12 (Folder 2, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "Poughkeepsie Celebrates 250th Year as Community", 1937 October 12 (Folder 3, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "Celebrating Poughkeepsie"s 250th Anniversary", 1937 October 12 (Folder 4, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "FDR Tells of City"s Heritage", 1937 October 13 (Folder 5, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "Highway to Follow New Route", 1937 October 14 (Folder 6, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "President Cancels His Appearance Here; Chamberlain Back Home", 1938 September 16 (Folder 7, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "President Calls for Faith in U.S.; France and Britain Plan Joint Answer to Hitler", 1938 September 17 (Folder 8, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "Pilot Lost in Army Plane Crash South of Hudson; Peace Conference Nears Collapse" (Also column by Eleanor Roosevelt), 1938 September 23 (Folder 9, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - "City Officials Study Relief Costs; Daladier Sees New Friendship Era for Europe", 1938 October 4 (Folder 10, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise -"Schwartz Studies Own County Quiz; Italy Claims Axis Partner in Yugoslavia", 1939 April 24 (Folder 11, Box 68)
      - Poughkeepsie Evening Star Enterprise - 50th Anniversary Edition, 1939 April 24 (Folder 12, Box 68)
    - Subseries 4.2.4: The New York World, 1889 - 1929; 4.2.4; Box: 69
      - The New York World - volume XXIX, number 10,148; "6,000 Dead - Johnstown Blotted Out by the Flood", 1889 June 2 (Folder 1, Box 69)
      - The New York World, 1929 March 8 (Folder 2, Box 69)
      - The New York World - St. Patrick, Ireland's Patron Saint, 1929 March 17 (Folder 3, Box 69)
      - The New York World - Sports Section, 1929 March 17 (Folder 4, Box 69)
      - The New York World - Editorial Section, 1929 March 17 (Folder 5, Box 69)
    - Subseries 4.2.5: Miscellany, 1847 - 1945; 4.2.5; Box: 70
      - Chicago Tribune - volume XIV, number 246 (1933 reprint), 1861 April 15 (actual printing 1933) (Folder 1, Box 70)
      - The Christian Science Monitor - volume XXIX, number 124, 1937 April 22 (Folder 2, Box 70)
      - The Fishkill Standard - Advertising for Poughkeepsie Merchants, undated (Folder 3, Box 70)
      - The Highland News - "Town Meeting-1845" (with 1853 map of Ulster County), 1945 May 3 (Folder 4, Box 70)
      - Journal American - "Dewey Agrees to Back O"Dwyer"s Plans for City; Truman, Attlee Open Atom Talks; Soviet Amity Feared in Balance", 1945 November 11 (Folder 5, Box 70)
      - Kingston Daily Freeman - "Poughkeepsians Here to Dine", 1923 May 14 (Folder 6, Box 70)
      - Kingston Daily Leader, 1923 May 14 (Folder 7, Box 70)
      - Morris County Daily Record - "Morris Views the Moon", 1969 July 21 (Folder 8, Box 70)
      - The New York Herald - "Important - Assassination of President Lincoln" (reprint with descriptive document), 1865 April 15 (actual printing unknown) (Folder 9, Box 70)
      - The Pawling Chronicle - "Pawling to Make War Boldly on the White House", 1933 August 5 (Folder 10, Box 70)
      - The Pawling News-Chronicle - volume LXX, number 42; includes articles on Thomas Dewey and Lowell Thomas, 1940 October 3 (Folder 11, Box 70)
      - Poughkeepsie New Yorker - Affidavit of Publication, 1944 (Folder 12, Box 70)
      - Rhinebeck Gazette - volume XXXVI, number 17 (in JSC-12), 1884 May 17 (Folder 13, Box 70)
      - Subscription to the Poughkeepsie Eagle, undated (Folder 14, Box 70)
      - Subscription to the Sunday Courier, 1919 August 5 (Folder 15, Box 70)
      - Vox Populi - whole number 2, 1890 June 12 (Folder 16, Box 70)
      - Vox Populi, undated (Folder 17, Box 70)
      - Unknown damaged paper, undated (Folder 18, Box 70)
      - Unknown Poughkeepsie Paper - volume 2, number 82 (sent with note to William Smith of Luckey, Platt and Co.) (in JSC-12), 1847 June 26 (Folder 19, Box 70)
  - Subseries 4.3: Scrapbooks, 1917 - 1985; 4.3; Boxes: 71 - 74
    - Luckey, Platt and Company Scrapbook, 1927 - 1941 (Folder 1, Box 71)
    - Headline News Scrapbook, 1937 - 1940 (Folder 1, Box 72)
    - Luckey, Platt and Company Scrapbook, 1952 - 1957 (Folder 1, Box 73)
    - Luckey, Platt and Company Scrapbook, 1917 - 1923 (Folder 1, Box 74)
    - Luckey, Platt and Company Scrapbook, 1923 - 1927 (Folder 2, Box 74)
    - Luckey, Platt and Company Scrapbook, 1941 - 1945 (Folder 3, Box 74)
    - Luckey, Platt and Company Scrapbook, 1949 - 1952 (Folder 4, Box 74)
    - Regatta Trophy Scrapbook, 1948 - 1950 (Folder 5, Box 74)
    - Scholastic Art Awards Scrapbook, 1948 - 1950 (Folder 6, Box 74)
    - Poughkeepsie Scrapbook with assorted clippings - focus on music, 1962 - 1984 (Folder 7, Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, 1981 - 1985 (Folder 8, Box 74)
    - Folder labeled Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 9, Box 74)
- 5. Books, 1871 - 2002; 5; Boxes: 75 - 84
  Series contains Local Histories, Local Publications, Dutchess County Historical Society, Other Local Organizations, Publications concerning Vassar College, Miscellany
  - Subseries 5.1: Local Histories, 1872 - 1987; 5.1; Boxes: 75 - 77
    - A Century of Music in Poughkeepsie, 1802 - 1911, 1912; Andrus, Helen Josephine (Folder 1, Box 75)
      Frank B. Howard
      Poughkeepsie, NY
    - Documents found with A Century of Music in Poughkeepsie, 1802 - 1911, undated; Rosenfeld, Paul and Kipling, Rudyard (Folder 2, Box 75)
      unknown
    - New York State Illustrated: The Tourist’s Guide Through the Empire State, 1872; Colt, SS., ed. (Folder 3, Box 75)
      S.S. Colt
      Albany, NY
    - Hudson Valley People: Albany to Yonkers, 1700 - 1900, 1982; Faison, Jr., S. Lane and Mills, Sally (Folder 4, Box 75)
      Vassar College Art Gallery
    - A Hudson Riverbook, 1980; Gekle, William (Folder 5, Box 75)
      Wyvern House; Hamilton Reproductions
    - The History of Dutchess County New York, 1909; Hasbrouck, Frank, ed. (Folder 1, Box 76)
      S.A Matthieu
    - Ice Harvesting in Early America, 1977; Hill, Dewey D., and Hughes, Elliott R. (Folder 1, Box 77)
      New Hartford Historical Society
      New Hartford, NY
    - Dutchess County: A Pictorial History, 1983; Jeanneney, John and Jeanneney, Mary L. (Folder 2, Box 77)
      The Donning Company/Publishers
      Norfolk/Virginia Beach
    - Blithe Dutchess: The Flowering of an American County from 1812, 1958; MacCracken, Henry Nobel (Folder 3, Box 77)
      Hastings House
      New York
    - Old Dutchess Forever!: The Story of an American County, 1956; MacCracken, Henry Nobel (Folder 4, Box 77)
    - The Eagle’s History of Poughkeepsie: From the Earliest Settlements, 1683 - 1905, Platt, Edmund (Folder 5, Box 77)
      Platt& Platt
    - The Eagle’s History of Poughkeepsie: From the Earliest Settlements, 1683 - 1905, 1987; Platt, Edmund (Folder 6, Box 77)
      Dutchess County Historical Society
    - Main Street, 1915; Salmon, Lucy M. (Folder 7, Box 77)
      Lucy M. Salmon
    - History of Dutchess County, New York: With Illustrations and Biographical Sketches of Some of its Prominent Men and Pioneers, 1683 - 1882, Smith, James H. (Folder 8, Box 77)
      D. Mason and Company
      Syracuse, NY
    - The Inner Life of an Inn: Being a True Story of an Inn near Vassar College, 1919; Wagner, Mary Swain (Folder 9, Box 77)
      A.V. Haight Company
  - Subseries 5.2: Local Publications, 1871 - 1954; 5.2; Boxes: 78 - 79
    - Tom Swift and his Airline Express, 1926; Appleton, Victor (Folder 1, Box 78)
      Whitman Publishing Company
      Racine, WI; Poughkeepsie, NY
    - Tom Swift and his Television Director, 1933; Appleton, Victor (Folder 2, Box 78)
    - E.H.: The Life Story of E.H. Wadewitz, undated; Black, Don H. (Folder 3, Box 78)
    - Miss Jemima, 1935; De La Mare, Walter (Folder 4, Box 78)
      Artists and Writers Guild, Inc.
    - Poems, 1914; Farrington, Walter (Folder 5, Box 78)
    - Parturition Without Pain: Code of Directions for Escaping from the Primal Curse, 1871; Holbrook, M.D., M.L, ed. (Folder 1, Box 79)
      Wood& Holbrook
    - The Pike: A Novel, 1954; Hoss, May Dikeman (Folder 2, Box 79)
      Appleton-Century-Crofts, Inc.
    - The Orchid, 1926; Noel, Joseph (Folder 3, Box 79)
      The New Play Publishing Company
    - Reminiscences: Personal and Professional, 1859 - 1939, circa 1939; Poucher, J. Wilson (Folder 4, Box 79)
      J. Wilson Poucher
    - Stories of the Wild Flowers, 1931; Poucher, J. Wilson (Folder 5, Box 79)
    - In the Land of the Romburg, 1906; Warren, Benjamin Clark (Folder 6, Box 79)
      Broadway Publishing Company
    - Documents found with In the Land of the Romburg, undated; Unknown (Folder 7, Box 79)
  - Subseries 5.3: Dutchess County Historical Society, 1948 - 2002; 5.3; Boxes: 80 - 81
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 33, 1948; Ver Nooy, Amy Pearce, ed. (Folder 1, Box 80)
      The Dutchess County Historical Society
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 54, 1969; Van Kleeck, Baltus B., ed. (Folder 2, Box 80)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 66, 1981; McDermott, William P., ed. (Folder 3, Box 80)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 67, 1982; McDermott, William P., ed. (Folder 4, Box 80)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 67, 1982; McDermott, William P., ed. (Folder 5, Box 80)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 68, 1983; McDermott, William P., ed. (Folder 6, Box 80)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 68, 1983; McDermott, William P., ed. (Folder 7, Box 80)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 69, 1984; McDermott, William P., ed. (Folder 8, Box 80)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 69, 1984; McDermott, William P., ed. (Folder 9, Box 80)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 70, 1985; Jeanneney, John and Jeanneney, Mary Lou, eds, (Folder 1, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 70, 1985; Jeanneney, John and Jeanneney, Mary Lou, eds, (Folder 2, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 71, 1986; Jeanneney, John and Jeanneney, Mary Lou, eds, (Folder 3, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 73, 1988; Jeanneney, John and Jeanneney, Mary Lou, eds, (Folder 4, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 74, 1989; Lytle, Mark H., ed. (Folder 5, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 75, 1990; Richardson, William N. and Begos, Jane D., eds. (Folder 6, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 78, 1993; Kushner, Carol, ed. (Folder 7, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 79, 1994; Kushner, Carol, ed. (Folder 8, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 80, 1995 - 1996; The Dutchess County Historical Society (Folder 9, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 81, 1997 - 1998; The Dutchess County Historical Society (Folder 10, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 82, 1999 - 2000; Fogel, Nan, ed. (Folder 11, Box 81)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 83, 2001 - 2002; Fogel, Nan, ed. (Folder 12, Box 81)
    - Hollow Oak Chronicles: The Van Vliets of Dutchess County; Dutchess County Historical Society Yearbook, Volume 84, 2003 - 2004; Fogel, Nan, ed. (Folder 13, Box 81)
    - The Glebe House, 1967; The Dutchess County Historical Society (Folder 14, Box 81)
      The Pendell Press
    - Marriages& Deaths, 1778 - 1825; Dutchess County, New York, Volume IV, 1982; Reynolds, Helen Wilkinson (Folder 15, Box 81)
      Gateway Press
      Baltimore
    - Catharyne Brett: Portrait of a Colonial Businesswoman, 1992; Cassidy, Henry (Folder 16, Box 81)
      Collections of the Dutchess County Historical Society
  - Subseries 5.4: Other Local Organizations, 1983 - 1993; 5.4; Box: 82
    - The Hudson Valley Regional Review: A Journal of Regional Studies, Volume 4, Number 2, 1987; Pierce, David C. and Wiles, Richard C., eds. (Folder 1, Box 82)
      The Bard Center
      Annandale-on-Hudson, NY
    - The Hudson Valley Regional Review: A Journal of Regional Studies, Volume 6, Number 1, 1989; Pierce, David C. and Wiles, Richard C., eds. (Folder 2, Box 82)
    - The Hudson Valley Regional Review: A Journal of Regional Studies, Volume 6, Number 2, 1989; Wiles, Richard C. and Wilson, William, eds. (Folder 3, Box 82)
    - The Hudson Valley Regional Review: A Journal of Regional Studies, Volume 7, Number 1, 1990; Wiles, Richard C. and Wilson, William, eds. (Folder 4, Box 82)
    - Her Star Still Shines: Eleanor Roosevelt Gala, 1993; Bassanese, Lynn A., and Metreaud, Michelle S., eds. (Folder 5, Box 82)
      A Franklin D. Roosevelt Library Publication
      Hyde Park, NY
    - Municipal Historians’ Book of Dutchess County: Tercentenary Edition, 1683 - 1983, Dutchess County Tercentenary Advisory Committee (Folder 6, Box 82)
      Dutchess County Tercentenary Advisor Committee
    - Documents found with Municipal Historians’ Book of Dutchess County: Tercentenary Edition, 1683 - 1983, Reprinted Map of Dutchess County, 1867 (Folder 7, Box 82)
      Dutchess County Municipal Historians Association
    - Directory of Historical Agencies, Museums and Local Historians for Dutchess, Putnam, Rockland and Westchester Counties, 1984; Lower Hudson Conference (Folder 8, Box 82)
      Guideposts Associations, Inc.
      Carmel, NY
  - Subseries 5.5: Publications concerning Vassar College, 1907 - 1984; 5.5; Box: 83
    - Letters from Old-Time Vassar, 1915; A Student (Folder 1, Box 83)
      Vassar College
    - Main to Mudd: An Informal History of Vassar College Buildings, 1987; Daniels, Elizabeth A. (Folder 2, Box 83)
    - Vassar: The Remarkable Growth of a Man and His College, 1855 - 1865, 1984; Linner, Edward R. (Folder 3, Box 83)
    - Vassar College and its Founder, 1867; Lossing, Benson J. (Folder 4, Box 83)
      C.A. Alvord
    - Documents found with Vassar College and its Founder, undated; Clippings (Folder 5, Box 83)
    - The Magnificent Enterprise: A Chronicle of Vassar College, 1961; Plum, Dorothy A., and Dowell, George B. (Folder 6, Box 83)
      Princeton University Press
      Princeton, NJ
    - Geological Rambles Near Vassar College, 1907; Shattuck, George Burbank, PhD. (Folder 7, Box 83)
      Vassar College Press
    - American College& University Series: Vassar, 1915; Taylor, James Monroe and Haight, Elizabeth Hazelton (Folder 8, Box 83)
      Oxford University Press
    - A Book of Vassar Verse, 1916; Vassar Miscellany Monthly (Folder 9, Box 83)
  - Subseries 5.6: Miscellany, 5.6; Box: 84
    - Eastman Business College Student Guide, 1868; Eastman Business College (Folder 1, Box 84)
      Isaac Platt& Son, Eagle Printing House
    - Catalog “K”, undated; Federal Ball Bearings (Folder 2, Box 84)
      Federal Ball Bearings
    - Catalog number 4, 1949; Nilsson Gage Company Inc. (Folder 3, Box 84)
      Nilsson Gage Company Inc.
    - Catalog number 10, circa 1943; Standard Gages (Folder 4, Box 84)
- 6. Ephemera, 1874 - 1945; 6; Boxes: 85 - 121
  Series contains Advertising and Postcard Collection, Newspaper advertisements, Other publications, and objects
  - Subseries 6.1: Advertising and Postcard Collection, 1874 - 1945; 6.1; Boxes: 85
    Series contains advertismenets and postcards
    - Subseries 6.1.1: Advertisements, 1874 - 1945; 6.1.1; Box: 85
      Series contains advertismenets for businesses and miscellany
      - Subseries 6.1.1.1: Businesses, 6.1.1.1; Box: 85
        Series contains materials from manufactueres, retail, service, and wholesale
        - Subseries 6.1.1.1.1: Manufacturers, 6.1.1.1.1; Box: 85
          - General, undated (Folder 1, Box 85)
          - Carriages, sleighs, harnesses and more, undated (Folder 2, Box 85)
          - Mowers, reapers (including Adriance and Platt), 1886 - 1889 (Folder 3, Box 85)
        - Subseries 6.1.1.1.2: Retail, 6.1.1.1.2; Box: 85
          - Art, photos, frames, portraits and more, circa 1892 (Folder 4, Box 85)
          - Booksellers, stationary, circa 1891 (Folder 5, Box 85)
          - Bicycles, undated (Folder 6, Box 85)
          - China, glassware, undated (Folder 7, Box 85)
          - Clothing, dry goods, undated (Folder 8, Box 85)
          - Department Stores - Luckey, Platt and Company, undated (Folder 9, Box 85)
          - Department Stores - Miscellany, undated (Folder 10, Box 85)
          - Druggists, undated (Folder 11, Box 85)
          - Florists, circa 1934 (Folder 12, Box 85)
          - Food, groceries - A P, undated (Folder 13, Box 85)
          - Food, groceries - Miscellany, 1922 - circa 1930s (Folder 14, Box 85)
          - Furniture (including undertakers), undated (Folder 15, Box 85)
          - Hats, millinery, undated (Folder 16, Box 85)
          - Hardware, sporting goods, house repair, guns, and more, undated (Folder 17, Box 85)
          - Jewelry, undated (Folder 18, Box 85)
          - Liquor, undated (Folder 19, Box 85)
          - Music, musical instruments, undated (Folder 20, Box 85)
          - Sewing machines, undated (Folder 21, Box 85)
          - Shoes, undated (Folder 22, Box 85)
          - Stoves, furnaces and more, undated (Folder 23, Box 85)
          - Tobacconists, undated (Folder 24, Box 85)
        - Subseries 6.1.1.1.3: Service, 6.1.1.1.3; Box: 85
          - Auto repair, circa 1945 (Folder 25, Box 85)
          - Beauty parlors, undated (Folder 26, Box 85)
          - Builders, masons, and more, circa 1952 (Folder 27, Box 85)
          - Cleaners, tailors, undated (Folder 28, Box 85)
          - Maids, housecleaning, undated (Folder 29, Box 85)
        - Subseries 6.1.1.1.4: Wholesale, 6.1.1.1.4; Box: 85
          - Dairy, undated (Folder 30, Box 85)
          - Food, groceries, undated (Folder 31, Box 85)
      - Subseries 6.1.1.2: Miscellany, 1874 - 1945; 6.1.1.2; Box: 85
        - Collage of early Poughkeepsie advertising, circa 1900s (Folder 32, Box 85)
        - Dentistry, undated (Folder 33, Box 85)
        - Insurance/Finance companies, undated (Folder 34, Box 85)
        - Newspapers, circa 1926 (Folder 35, Box 85)
        - Opticians, undated (Folder 36, Box 85)
        - Politics, 1876 - 1936 (Folder 37, Box 85)
        - Radio Television, undated (Folder 38, Box 85)
        - Restaurants, undated (Folder 39, Box 85)
        - Utilities, 1874 - circa 1945 (Folder 40, Box 85)
    - Subseries 6.1.2: Postcards, 1904 - 2002; 6.1.2; Boxes: 85 - 87
      - Subseries 6.1.2.1: Postcard album, 6.1.2.1; Box: 86
        - Album that contained Postcards, undated (Folder 21, Box 86)
        - Postcards from album, listed alphabetically, a-z, various (Folder 22, Box 86)
      - Banks, circa 1922 (Folder 40, Box 85)
      - Bridges, 1904 - 1946 (Folder 41, Box 85)
      - Businesses - Luckey, Platt and Company, circa 1908 (Folder 42, Box 85)
      - Businesses - Miscellany, undated (Folder 43, Box 85)
      - Dutchess County, 1906 - 2002 (Folder 44, Box 85)
      - Education - Vassar College, undated (Folder 45, Box 85)
      - Education - Vassar Institute, 1906 - 1908 (Folder 46, Box 85)
      - Education - Miscellany, 1903 - 1930 (Folder 1, Box 86)
      - Hospitals (including homes), 1906 - 1930 (Folder 2, Box 86)
      - Hotels and Inns (including restaurants), 1906 - 1952 (Folder 3, Box 86)
      - Houses and Buildings - Armory, 1906 - 1919 (Folder 4, Box 86)
      - Houses and Buildings - Burroughs Home ("Slab Sides"), 1908 - 1912 (Folder 5, Box 86)